Hello.

My name is John Damits

I have a passion for using code and digital design in non-traditional ways, especially by combining the creative aspects of Computer Science with my Asian Studies experience in order to foster inter-cultural understanding.

Tel: (724) 209-8709 Mail: hello@idamits.com Portfolio: https://jdamits.com

Experience

Atlantic Nitrogen & Testing | Engineer 5.2013 - Present

• In charge of software development process involving pipeline integrity testing

Designed and built websites and data server for the company

https://atlanticn2.com and http://atlanticnitrogen.com

Link2Launch | Software Engineer 1.2017 - 8.2018

6.2016 - 8.2016 **Knox College CS Department** | Research Internship

• Worked with Java, HTML, CSS, and Javascript to create a teaching tool

Designed the website for the project

https://sites.google.com/a/knox.edu/knoxcraft/

6.2015 - 8.2015 **Zego Robotics** | Software Engineer, Designer

• Designed and built robots for a robotics company in Pittsburgh

• 3D modeled and build a prototype human assistance robot

02. Education



Knox College | Bachelor of Arts Computer Science + Asian Studies KNOX GPA: **3.91** - Summa Cum Laude



Case Western Reserve University

Computer Science

GPA: 3.03

03. Skills and Accomplishments

Languages English | Japanese | Java | C/C++ | Python | HTML | CSS | Javascript

Coursework **Software Development** | Worked in an AGILE team

> **Parallel Programming** | Parallelization of large cluster systems **Cognition and Design** | Approaches to design and programming

Senior Patrol Leader | Troop 58 **Eagle Scout**

President | Organized weekly meetings, I-Fair, and club trips Japanese Club

Phi Beta Kappa **National Honors Society** Smash Bros. Club **Founder and President**

Research Assistant Professor Amy Absher | Case Western Reserve University

Professor Jaime Spacco | Knox College